{
    "subject": "resource/Nia_Long",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Brooklyn",
    "human_readable": "Nia Long was born in Brooklyn.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8139175772666931,
            "question": "Where was Nia Long born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7390170693397522,
            "question": "When was Nia Long born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6289212107658386,
            "question": "In what US state was Nia Long born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5593701004981995,
            "question": "Which borough of New York City is Nia Long from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4068484604358673,
            "question": "What is Nia Long known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2841263711452484,
            "question": "What is the name of Nia Long's son?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21033264696598053,
            "question": "Has Nia Long ever won an award for her acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16814035177230835,
            "question": "Is Nia Long known for her work on television as well?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11234453320503235,
            "question": "What type of roles is Nia Long often cast in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10368680953979492,
            "question": "Name some of Nia Long's most popular films."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nia Long was born in Brooklyn.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7727_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of roles is Nia Long often cast in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7727_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Nia Long known for her work on television as well?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7727_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Nia Long ever won an award for her acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7727_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7727_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7727_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7727_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7727_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7727_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7727_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7727_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7727_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7727_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7727_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Nia Long was born in Brooklyn. All four relevant documents mention that Nia Long was born in Brooklyn, New York, U.S., and two of them specify her birthplace as Brooklyn, NY (first document) or Brooklyn, New York, U.S. (three other documents)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Nia Long was born in Brooklyn, New York. Therefore, the triple stating that Nia Long was born in Brooklyn is correct according to the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}